



Javad **Haditaghi** Web Developer & Data Analyst

Mashhad, Iran

☑ javadht1990a@gmail.com

\& +98 937-606-8193

SOCIAL

in @javad-haditaghi

Javad Haditaghi

PERSONAL INFO

DOB: 22 September 1990

Nationality: Iranian

PROFILE

A multidisciplinary researcher, as demonstrated by merging network theory with discourse analysis using Computational Linguistics, resulting in 1 publication in a peer-reviewed scientific journal

An eager data analyst who performed multiple analyses using deep learning and machine learning methods.

A highly qualified web developer striving to implement artificial intelligence techniques to enhance user experience and website performance.

An ambitious teacher and writer who has evaluated a significant number of teaching methods and writing techniques to apply in an academic environment

EDUCATION

M.A. IN ENGLISH TEACHING

From 2015 to 2018 | Guilan University

Supervised by Dr. Jaleh Hassaskhah

Thesis Title: A corpus linguistic approach to the study of the voices in the text in light of Laclau and Mouffe's discourse theory

*A synopsis of the work undertaken is attached as an appendix.

B.A. IN ENGLISH TRANSLATION

From 2010 to 2014 |

PUBLICATIONS

A NETWORK-BASED APPROACH FOR DISCOURSE ANALYSIS FROM LACLAU AND MOUFFE'S PERSPECTIVES.

Haditaghi, J., Hassasskhah, J., & Sorahi, M. (2020). A network-based approach for discourse analysis from Laclau and Mouffe's perspectives. Journal of Computer-Assisted Linguistic Research, 4(1), 1-22.

Click for DOI

SIGNIFIER, RELATION AND TEXT: A NETWORK-BASED APPROACH FOR SEMANTIC CONTENT ANALYSIS

Accepted but not published

TEST SCORES

■ TOEFL TEST SCORE

October 2022

Listening: 29 | Reading: 29 | Speaking: 25 | Writing: 30

Overal Score: 113

RESEARCH INTERSTS

- Network Theory
- Computational Linguistics
- · Complex Theory
- Natural Language Processing
- Machine Learning
- Deep Learning
- · Interdisciplinary Approaches
- Data Analysis

SKILLS

Programming

HTML
 Python

CSS
 Pandas

Sass
 Matplotlib

JavaScriptNumpy

JquerySeaborn

Bootstrap
 Pytorch

React • Scikitlearn

OpenCV

Other Skills

Using Gephi
 Content Writing

· Microsoft Office · Webscraping

EXPERIENCE

TEAM MANAGER | DEKA TEAM

Deka Team

2023 - NOW

Develop and implement a strategic roadmap for the integration of AI technologies into web development projects, ensuring alignment with company objectives and industry best practices.

WEB DEVELOPER & DATA ANALYST

Golden Nutrition LLC

2020 - Now

Conduct comprehensive data analysis to identify trends, patterns, and insights, leveraging statistical techniques and data mining tools to optimize business processes and drive informed decision-making.

WEB DEVELOPER

Freelancer

2018 - Now

Collaborate with clients to conceptualize, design, and implement intuitive user interfaces and responsive web applications, ensuring a seamless user experience as a freelance front-end developer.

ENGLISH TEACHER

Different Institutes in Mashhad

2012 - Now

Develop and deliver comprehensive English language lessons to students across various institutes in Mashhad, ensuring a dynamic and engaging learning environment.

CERTIFICATE

Certified for compliance in the work area (2012)

For meeting the expectations of leading the team to work the specified tasks in the labor field.

Certificate of attendance on computer technology.

For meeting the expectations of leading the team to work the specified tasks in the labor field.

Achievement medal for productivity excellence during the year (2019)

For meeting the expectations of leading the team to work the specified tasks in the labor field.

REFERENCES

Dr. Jaleh Hassaskhah (My M.A. thesis advisor)

Associate professor, Department of English Language & Literature

Guilan University, Rasht, Iran

Phone: 000-000-0000*

Email: jaleh_hassaskhah@yahoo.com

Dr. Abdorreza Tahriri (My M.A. thesis referee & course professor)

Associate professor, Department of English Language and Literature

Guilan University, Rasht, Iran

Phone: 000-000-0000* Email: atahriri@gmail.com

Dr. Mohammad Amin Sorahi (My M.A. thesis Co-Supervisor)

Assistant professor, Department of English Language and Literature

Guilan University, Rasht, Iran

Phone: 000-000-0000*

Email: aminsorahi@hotmail.com

LANGUAGES

- Persian (Native)
 English (C2)
 German (A1)

INTERESTS

7

?

Classical Music

Travel

Reading Conceptual Art